{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295783094","data":{"timestamp":" 947295783094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295783469","data":{"timestamp":" 947295783469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295783957","data":{"timestamp":" 947295783957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295784305","data":{"timestamp":" 947295784305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295784714","data":{"timestamp":" 947295784714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295785188","data":{"timestamp":" 947295785188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295785415","data":{"timestamp":" 947295785415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295788579","data":{"timestamp":" 947295788579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295788613","data":{"timestamp":" 947295788613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295789326","data":{"timestamp":" 947295789326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295789720","data":{"timestamp":" 947295789720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295790013","data":{"timestamp":" 947295790013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295790217","data":{"timestamp":" 947295790217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295790411","data":{"timestamp":" 947295790411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295790725","data":{"timestamp":" 947295790725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295790948","data":{"timestamp":" 947295790948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295794101","data":{"timestamp":" 947295794101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295794504","data":{"timestamp":" 947295794503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295797002","data":{"timestamp":" 947295797002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295797206","data":{"timestamp":" 947295797206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295797409","data":{"timestamp":" 947295797409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295800826","data":{"timestamp":" 947295800826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295804502","data":{"timestamp":" 947295804502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295805525","data":{"timestamp":" 947295805525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295808208","data":{"timestamp":" 947295808208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295808582","data":{"timestamp":" 947295808582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295809064","data":{"timestamp":" 947295809064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295809407","data":{"timestamp":" 947295809407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295809811","data":{"timestamp":" 947295809811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295810284","data":{"timestamp":" 947295810284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295810508","data":{"timestamp":" 947295810508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295813688","data":{"timestamp":" 947295813688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295813721","data":{"timestamp":" 947295813721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295814435","data":{"timestamp":" 947295814435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295814828","data":{"timestamp":" 947295814828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295815121","data":{"timestamp":" 947295815121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295815325","data":{"timestamp":" 947295815325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295815519","data":{"timestamp":" 947295815518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295815832","data":{"timestamp":" 947295815832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295816055","data":{"timestamp":" 947295816055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295818693","data":{"timestamp":" 947295818693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295818750","data":{"timestamp":" 947295818750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 67fe454b-4280-4161-829e-40752226e77d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295833088","data":{"timestamp":" 947295833087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295835492","data":{"timestamp":" 947295835492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295837118","data":{"timestamp":" 947295837117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295842073","data":{"timestamp":" 947295842073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295843640","data":{"timestamp":" 947295843639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295850351","data":{"timestamp":" 947295850351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295851983","data":{"timestamp":" 947295851982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295854855","data":{"timestamp":" 947295854854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295856472","data":{"timestamp":" 947295856471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295859791","data":{"timestamp":" 947295859791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295861433","data":{"timestamp":" 947295861432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295865497","data":{"timestamp":" 947295865497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295867079","data":{"timestamp":" 947295867079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295870421","data":{"timestamp":" 947295870421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295871990","data":{"timestamp":" 947295871990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295875381","data":{"timestamp":" 947295875381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295876962","data":{"timestamp":" 947295876962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295879873","data":{"timestamp":" 947295879873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295881488","data":{"timestamp":" 947295881487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295884077","data":{"timestamp":" 947295884077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295885693","data":{"timestamp":" 947295885693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295888669","data":{"timestamp":" 947295888668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295890295","data":{"timestamp":" 947295890294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295892896","data":{"timestamp":" 947295892895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295894521","data":{"timestamp":" 947295894521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295897653","data":{"timestamp":" 947295897652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295899679","data":{"timestamp":" 947295899678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295899800","data":{"timestamp":" 947295899800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 6615717d-8858-49be-a8fd-0965b7273b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295914168","data":{"timestamp":" 947295914167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295916730","data":{"timestamp":" 947295916730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295918323","data":{"timestamp":" 947295918322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295924070","data":{"timestamp":" 947295924069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295925679","data":{"timestamp":" 947295925678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295928132","data":{"timestamp":" 947295928132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295929757","data":{"timestamp":" 947295929756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295932438","data":{"timestamp":" 947295932438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295934061","data":{"timestamp":" 947295934059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295939674","data":{"timestamp":" 947295939674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295941284","data":{"timestamp":" 947295941284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295943865","data":{"timestamp":" 947295943864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295945485","data":{"timestamp":" 947295945484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295948052","data":{"timestamp":" 947295948051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295949675","data":{"timestamp":" 947295949674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295951960","data":{"timestamp":" 947295951960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295953570","data":{"timestamp":" 947295953569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295958150","data":{"timestamp":" 947295958150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295959759","data":{"timestamp":" 947295959758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295964093","data":{"timestamp":" 947295964093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295965703","data":{"timestamp":" 947295965702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295970430","data":{"timestamp":" 947295970430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295972038","data":{"timestamp":" 947295972037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295974755","data":{"timestamp":" 947295974754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295976352","data":{"timestamp":" 947295976352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295978999","data":{"timestamp":" 947295978998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" START_PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295981046","data":{"timestamp":" 947295981046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295983065","data":{"timestamp":" 947295983063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947295983184","data":{"timestamp":" 947295983183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 0ce1d4e9-6c63-49c5-b3bc-d02a93840765"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296000284","data":{"timestamp":" 947296000283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296002578","data":{"timestamp":" 947296002578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296004140","data":{"timestamp":" 947296004139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296008519","data":{"timestamp":" 947296008519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296010146","data":{"timestamp":" 947296010145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296012900","data":{"timestamp":" 947296012899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296014526","data":{"timestamp":" 947296014526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296018442","data":{"timestamp":" 947296018441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296020045","data":{"timestamp":" 947296020044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296022981","data":{"timestamp":" 947296022980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296024606","data":{"timestamp":" 947296024605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296036876","data":{"timestamp":" 947296036875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296038496","data":{"timestamp":" 947296038496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296042117","data":{"timestamp":" 947296042117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296043724","data":{"timestamp":" 947296043724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296046422","data":{"timestamp":" 947296046421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296048034","data":{"timestamp":" 947296048033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296051273","data":{"timestamp":" 947296051272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296052888","data":{"timestamp":" 947296052887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296055492","data":{"timestamp":" 947296055491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296057104","data":{"timestamp":" 947296057103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296059941","data":{"timestamp":" 947296059940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296061556","data":{"timestamp":" 947296061555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296070402","data":{"timestamp":" 947296070401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296072037","data":{"timestamp":" 947296072037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296077708","data":{"timestamp":" 947296077707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296079737","data":{"timestamp":" 947296079735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296079887","data":{"timestamp":" 947296079886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_044243"," gameId":" 4a9bb314-c3f2-4409-bca9-046629e8cb5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}